[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Good morning!
Come on, let's eat.
Here. I'll serve you.
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll do it.
Why?
You also like leftover rice?
[JUNE] Nice.
Hey! Save some for me!
- Wait.
- Hey!
- You're selfish!
- Stop!
Hey! I want some too!
Oh my god!
I hope my hair doesn't
smell like tocino.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Hey! That's mine!
My brother also likes
leftover rice.
Back then, he'd only steal
- But now--
- You have a brother?
Good for you.
I'm an only child.
Are you two close?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Here.
Ima-Asim Homemade Vinegar.
At your service.
I'll give you even though you
took my leftover rice.
If you make a sour face,
you're mine.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUNE] Hmm?
It's sour, isn't it?
Hey! That's cheating!
I told you that the tocino and
vinegar complement each other.
Just like us.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
We both grew up poor.
The only difference is that
I have a bigger family,
so I don't always have
enough money.
It's not your job
to take care of them.
You're teaching them to be
dependent on you,
and that's why you couldn't
get ahead in life.
No one else would help us...
so we depend
on each other.
It's useless getting rich
by myself.
I'd rather not get rich if it
means turning back on family.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]